Hello!

This is a repo with my first few VHDL projects. These are all simulated on GHDL and waveforms are viewed through gtkwave. I unfortunately don't have a board right now so... it's all simulation now :/

I'm currently a Freshman Computer Engineering student at UCSC. I'm having a lot of fun trying my hand at Digital Design and am learning a lot. Hopefully, this will serve as a time capsule that I can look back upon in nostalgic frustration when I get good at VHDL and FPGA design :D